backdoors.to 2011-05-08

# Backdoors.To Privacy Policy

| 

**  Backdoors.To Privacy Policy**

At Backdoors.To we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all the products and services offered by Backdoors.To.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us.

**Information we collect and how we use it:**

We offer several services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, such as Backdoors.To Search. In order to provide all our services, we may collect the following types of information:

  * **Information you provide:** When you sign up for an Account or other service that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, we also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information. 

  * **Backdoors.To cookies:** When you visit Backdoors.To, we send one or more cookies (a small file containing a string of characters) to your computer that uniquely identifies your web browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features and services at Backdoors.To may not function properly if your browser's cookies are disabled. 

  * **Web log information:** When you use Backdoors.To services, our servers automatically record information that your web browser sends whenever you visit a web site. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, browser plug-ins, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

  * **User communications:** When you send email or other communication to Backdoors.To, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

  * **Affiliated web sites:** We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those web sites may be sent to Backdoors.To in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 
  * **Web links:** Backdoors.To may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search services and web site content. For information about links and redirected URLs, please see our Privacy FAQs. 

  * **Other web sites:** This Privacy Policy applies to all services that operated by Backdoors.To. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

Backdoors.To only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising;
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our web site and the services it provides; and
  * Developing new services.

**Choices for personal information**

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Backdoors.To may not be able to provide those services to you.

**Information sharing**

Backdoors.To only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Backdoors.To in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 
  * We provide such information to our sister companies, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually.

However, these third parties may place and read cookies on your browser, or may use web beacons to collect information, in the course of displaying certain parts of Backdoors.To pages.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Backdoors.To. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this website and to other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Google, as a third party advertising vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website. In this respect, please note the following:

  * Google's use of the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to our website users based on their visit to our website and other websites on the Internet. 
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures.

We restrict access to personal information to Backdoors.To employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Data integrity**

Backdoors.To processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

**Enforcement**

Backdoors.To regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or our treatment of personal information by contacting us.

**Changes to this policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.

| |  | My Favorites Games  
---  
| •  | Visited Games: Help   
Yahoo Pool  
Pogo Pool  
Yahoo Backgammon  
Yahoo Chess  
Yahoo France  
---|---  
Gaming Leagues  
| •  |  Favorite League [select]  
---|---  
• | Leagues List  
• | Submit your League  
• | [Create a League](http://www.leaga.com/)  
• | [Eliters.com](http://www.eliters.com/)  
Game Resources  
| • | Game Jargon  
---|---
